RG 002:004, General Assembly Papers
Connecticut State Library
- 2002-2004, 2007-008
  - 2003
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 52)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 53)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 54)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 55)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Higher Education and Employment Advancement (Box 56)
    - Unfinished Business - Housing; Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 57)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 58)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 59)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 360)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees (Box 61)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Planning and Development; Program Review and Investigations (Box 62)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health (Box 63)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation (Box 64)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; No Committee Name (Box 65)
    - Unfinished Business - Committee Transmittal Letters for Unfinished Business and Resolutions; Draft List of Unfinished Business Bills and Resolutions; Reports to the General Assembly (Box 66)
  - 2004
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 67)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 67)
    - Appointment Resolutions (Box 67)
    - Trailer Session Resolutions (Box 667)
    - Public Acts, 1-38 (Box 68)
    - Public Acts, 39-70 (Box 69)
    - Public Acts, 71-107 (Box 70)
    - Public Acts, 108-136 (Box 71)
    - Public Acts, 137-155 (Box 72)
    - Public Acts, 156-186 (Box 73)
    - Public Acts, 187-206 (Box 74)
    - Public Acts, 207-220 (Box 75)
    - Public Acts, 221-240 (Box 76)
    - Public Acts, 241-258 (Box 77)
    - Special Acts, 1-0 (Box 78)
    - Special Session, May 6 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 78)
    - Special Session, May - Adopted Resolutions (Box 78)
    - Special Session, May - Public Acts, 1-3 (Box 78)
    - Special Session, May - Special Acts, 1-2 (Box 78)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging; Appropriations (Box 79)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 80)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 81)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 82)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 83)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banking; Children; Commerce (Box 84)
    - Unfinished Business - Commerce; Education; Energy and Technology (Box 85)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Executive and Legislative Nominations; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 86)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 87)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 88)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding; General Law (Box 89)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 90)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Higher Education and Employment Advancement; Housing (Box 91)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 92)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 93)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 94)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 95)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management (Box 96)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 97)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Program Review and Investigations; Public Health (Box 98)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health (Box 99)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation; No Committee Name (Box 100)
    - Unfinished Business - Committee Transmittal Letters for Unfinished Business and Resolutions; Draft List of Unfinished Business Bills and Resolutions; Reports to the General Assembly (Box 101)
- 2005-2007, 2010-019
  - 2005
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Adopted Resolutions - Joint Convention; Senate; Senate Joint (Box 1)
    - Adopted Resolutions - House; House Joint (Box 2)
    - Adopted Resolutions - House Joint (Box 3)
    - January 2005 Trailer Session - Adopted Resolutions (Box 3)
    - Public Acts, 1-50 (Box 4)
    - Public Acts, 51-96 (Box 5)
    - Public Acts, 97-126 (Box 6)
    - Public Acts, 127-155 (Box 7)
    - Public Acts, 156-177 (Box 8)
    - Public Acts, 178-195 (Box 9)
    - Public Acts, 196-213 (Box 10)
    - Public Acts, 214-234 (Box 11)
    - Public Acts, 235-247 (Box 12)
    - Public Acts, 248-259 (Box 13)
    - Public Acts, 260-278 (Box 14)
    - Public Acts, 279-286 (Box 15)
    - Public Acts, 287-290 (Box 16)
    - Special Acts, 1-14 (Box 17)
    - Special Session, June - Adopted Resolutions (Box 18)
    - Special Session, June - Public Acts, 1-6 (Box 18)
    - Special Session, June - Special Act, 1 (Box 18)
    - Special Session, October 11 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 19)
    - Special Session, October 25 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 19)
    - Special Session, October 25 - Public Acts, 1-5 (Box 19)
    - Special Session, October 25 - Trailer Session Adopted Resolutions (Box 19)
    - Special Session, November 2 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 19)
    - Special Session, November 2 - Public Acts, 1-3 (Box 19)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging; Appropriations (Box 20)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 21)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 22)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banking (Box 23)
    - Unfinished Business - Children; Commerce; Education (Box 24)
    - Unfinished Business - Education (Box 25)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Technology; Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 26)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 27)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 28)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 29)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 30)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 31)
    - Unfinished Business - Higher Education; Housing; Human Services (Box 32)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate (Box 33)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 34)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 35)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 36)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 37)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management (Box 38)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development (Box 39)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health (Box 40)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety (Box 41)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 42)
    - Unfinished Business - Veterans' Affairs (Box 43)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SJR-31 to SJR-41, HR-16 to HR35, HJR 31-HJR115, SB-24 to SB-124 (Box 44)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SB200 to SB1117 (Box 45)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SB-1149 to SB-1338, HB-5040 to HB-5567 (Box 46)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5585 to HB-6589 (Box 47)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-6613 to HB-6714 (Box 48)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-6759 to HB-6879 (Box 49)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-6892 to HB-7001 (Box 50)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-27 to SB-1015 (Box 51)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-1023 to SB-1064 (Box 52)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-1081 to SB-1237 (Box 53)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-1239 to SB-1386, HB-5594 to HB-6663 (Box 54)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, HB-6670 to HB-6969 (Box 55)
  - 2006
    - Adopted Resolutions - Joint Convention; Senate; Senate Joint; House; House Joint (Box 56)
    - Adopted Resolutions; House Joint (Box 57)
    - Trailer Session - Resolutions (Box 57)
    - Public Acts, 1-12 (Box 57)
    - Public Acts, 13-45 (Box 58)
    - Public Acts, 46-68 (Box 59)
    - Public Acts, 69-86 (Box 60)
    - Public Acts, 87-120 (Box 61)
    - Public Acts, 121-136 (Box 62)
    - Public Acts, 137-154 (Box 63)
    - Public Acts, 155-172 (Box 64)
    - Public Acts, 173-187 (Box 65)
    - Public Acts, 188-195 (Box 66)
    - Public Acts, 196 (Box 67)
    - Special Acts, 1-10 (Box 67)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging; Appropriations (Box 68)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 69)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 70)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 71)
    - Unfinished Business - Banking; Children; Commerce (Box 72)
    - Unfinished Business - Education (Box 73)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Technology; Environment; Executive and Legislative Nominations (Box 74)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 75)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 76)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 77)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Higher Education; Housing; Human Services (Box 78)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 879)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 80)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 81)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 82)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management; Planning and Development; Program Review and Investigations (Box 83)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety (Box 84)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; Veterans' Affairs (Box 85)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SJR-5, HR-3 to HR-35, SB-31 to SB-408 (Box 86)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SB-417 to SB-648, HB-5007 to HB-5079 (Box 87)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5096 to HB-5559 (Box 88)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5595 to HB-5835 (Box 89)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SR-32, SJR-3, SB-1 to SB-435 (Box 90)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-465 to SB-701; HB-5016 to HB-5796 (Box 91)
  - 2007
    - Adopted Resolutions - Joint Convention; Senate; Senate Joint; House; House Joint (Box 92)
    - Adopted Resolutions - House Joint (Box 93)
    - Trailer Session Resolutions (Box 93)
    - Public Acts, 1-47 (Box 94)
    - Public Acts, 48-85 (Box 95)
    - Public Acts, 86-109 (Box 96)
    - Public Acts, 110-131 (Box 97)
    - Public Acts, 132-150 (Box 98)
    - Public Acts, 151-167 (Box 99)
    - Public Acts, 168-188 (Box 100)
    - Public Acts, 189-207 (Box 101)
    - Public Acts, 208-230 (Box 102)
    - Public Acts, 231-242 (Box 103)
    - Public Acts, 243-250 (Box 104)
    - Public Acts, 251-255 (Box 105)
    - Special Acts, 1-11 (Box 105)
    - Special Session, June - Resolutions (Box 106)
    - Special Session, June - Public Acts, 1-4 (Box 106)
    - Special Session, June - Public Acts, 5-7 (Box 107)
    - Special Session, September - Resolutions (Box 108)
    - Special Session, September - Public Act, 1 (Box 108)
    - Special Session, January 2008 - Resolutions (Box 108)
    - Special Session, January 2008 - Public Act, 1 (Box 108)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging; Appropriations (Box 109)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 110)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 111)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 112)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 113)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 114)
    - Unfinished Business - Banking; Children; Commerce (Box 115)
    - Unfinished Business - Education (Box 116)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Technology (Box 117)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment (Box 118)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 119)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 120)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 121)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law (Box 122)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 123)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 124)
    - Unfinished Business - Higher Education and Employment Advancement; Housing (Box 125)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services (Box 126)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate (Box 127)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 128)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 129)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 130)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 131)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 132)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development (Box 133)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety (Box 134)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 135)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; Veterans' Affairs (Box 136)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SJR-33, HR-47 to HR-65, HJR-2 to HJR-147, SB-5 to SB-1031 (Box 137)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SB-1044 to Sb-1307 (Box 138)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SB-1312 to SB-1485, HB-5016 to HB-5120 (Box 139)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5121 to HB-6642 (Box 140)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-6652 to HB-7000 (Box 141)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-7019 to HB-7097 (Box 142)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-7098 to HB-7137 (Box 143)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-7144 to HB-7315 (Box 144)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-7320 to HB-7426 (Box 145)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-7429 to HB-7434 (Box 146)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SJR-5, HJR-11 to HJR-165, SB-1 to SB-116 (Box 147)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-125 to SB-1059 (Box 148)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-1087 to SB-1183 (Box 149)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-1094 to SB-1328 (Box 150)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-1329 to SB-1372 (Box 151)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-1373 to SB-1448 (Box 152)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-1450 to SB-1476, SB-5539 to HB-7335 (Box 153)
    - Unfinished Business - Special Session, June 2007 (Box 154)
- 2008-2009, 2012-020
  - 2008
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Trailer Session Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Public Acts, 1-31 (Box 2)
    - Public Acts, 32-57 (Box 3)
    - Public Acts, 58-91 (Box 4)
    - Public Acts, 92-113 (Box 5)
    - Public Acts, 114-137 (Box 6)
    - Public Acts, 138-164 (Box 7)
    - Public Acts, 165-175 (Box 8)
    - Public Acts, 176-182 (Box 9)
    - Public Acts, 183-187 (Box 10)
    - Special Acts, 1-9 (Box 11)
    - Special Session, June 11 - Resolutions (Box 12)
    - Special Session, June 11 - Public Acts, 1-3 (Box 12)
    - Special Session, June 11 - Special Act, 1 (Box 12)
    - Special Session, August - Resolutions (Box 12)
    - Special Session, August - Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 12)
    - Special Session, August - Unfinished Business, No Committee Name (Box 12)
    - Special Session, November 24 - Resolutions (Box 12)
    - Special Session, November 24 - Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 12)
    - Special Session, November 24 - Unfinished Business, No Committee Name (Box 12)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging, Appropriations (Box 13)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 14)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banking; Children; Commerce (Box 15)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Energy and Technology; Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 16)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 17)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 18)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections; Higher Education and Employment Advancement; Housing; Human Services (Box 19)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 20)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 21)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 22)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety; Transportation; Veterans' Affairs (Box 23)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, Resolutions, SB-30 to SB-287 (Box 24)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SB-301 to SB-420 (Box 25)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SB-440 to SB-590 (Box 26)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SB-601 to SB-702 (Box 27)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5019 to HB-5519 (Box 28)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5531 to HB-5698 (Box 29)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5700 to HB5843 (Box 30)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5844 to HB-5940 (Box 31)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, Resolutions, SB-22 to SB-188 (Box 32)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-201 to SB-428 (Box 33)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-435 to SB-595 (Box 34)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-600 to SB-708 (Box 35)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, HB-5049 to HB-5930 (Box 36)
  - 2009
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 37)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 37)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 38)
    - Trailer Session Resolutions (Box 38)
    - Public Acts, 1-31 (Box 28)
    - Public Acts, 32-59 (Box 40)
    - Public Acts, 60-95 (Box 41)
    - Public Acts, 96-118 (Box 42)
    - Public Acts, 119-147 (Box 43)
    - Public Acts, 148-156 (Box 44)
    - Public Acts, 157-184 (Box 45)
    - Public Acts, 185-206 (Box 46)
    - Public Acts, 207-213 (Box 47)
    - Public Acts, 214-225 (Box 48)
    - Public Acts, 226-235 (Box 49)
    - Public Acts, 236-243 (Box 50)
    - Special Acts, 1-16 (Box 51)
    - Special Session, June - Adopted Resolutions (Box 52)
    - Special Session, June, Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 52)
    - Special Session, June, Public Acts, 3 (Box 53)
    - Special Session, June 19 - Adopted Resolutions (Box 54)
    - Special Session, June 19 - Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 54)
    - Special Session, September - Adopted Resolutions (Box 54)
    - Special Session, September - Public Acts, 1-5 (Box 54)
    - Special Session, September, Public Acts, 6-10 (Box 55)
    - Special Session, December - Adopted Resolutions (Box 56)
    - Special Session, December - Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 56)
    - Special Session Veto Session, December - Adopted Resolutions (Box 56)
    - Unfinished Business - Aging; Appropriations (Box 57)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 58)
    - Unfinished Business - Banking; Children; Commerce (Box 59)
    - Unfinished Business - Education (Box 60)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Technology (Box 61)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment (Box 62)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 63)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 64)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 65)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding; General Law (Box 66)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 67)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 68)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 69)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 70)
    - Unfinished Business - Higher Education and Employment Advancement; Housing; Human Services (Box 71)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 72)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 73)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 74)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 75)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management; Planning and Development, Senate (Box 76)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development, House; Program Review and Investigations; Public Health (Box 77)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation (Box 78)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; Veterans' Affairs (Box 79)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, Resolutions, SB-34 to SB-886 (Box 80)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SB-938 to HB-5416 (Box 81)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5425 to HB-6152 (Box 82)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-6188 to HB-6365 (Box 83)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-6373 to HB-6405 (Box 84)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-6407 to HB-6526 (Box 85)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-6534 to HB-6628 (Box 86)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-6632 to HB-6720 (Box 87)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, Resolutions, SB-1 to SB-561 (Box 88)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-609 to SB-834 (Box 89)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-841 to SB-909 (Box 90)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-910 to SB-939 (Box 91)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-947 to SB-1049 (Box 92)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-1058 to SB-1148 (Box 93)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-1152 to HB-5824 (Box 94)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, HB-5949 to HB-6338 (Box 95)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, HB-6413 to HB-6440 (Box 96)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, HB-6444 to HB-6529 (Box 97)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, HB-6535 to HB-6659 (Box 98)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, HB-6664 to HB-6710 (Box 99)
- 2010, 2013-023
  - 2010
    - Adopted Resolutions - Joint Convention, Senate, Senate Joint, House; House Joint to 85 (Box 1)
    - Adopted Resolutions - House Joint, 86-115 (Box 2)
    - Veto Session Resolutions (Box 2)
    - Public Acts, 1-10 (Box 2)
    - Public Acts, 11-32 (Box 3)
    - Public Acts, 33-44 (Box 4)
    - Public Acts, 45-75 (Box 5)
    - Public Acts, 76-98 (Box 6)
    - Public Acts, 99-110 (Box 7)
    - Public Acts, 111-121 (Box 8)
    - Public Acts, 122-141 (Box 9)
    - Public Acts, 142-170 (Box 10)
    - Public Acts, 171-180 (Box 11)
    - Public Acts, 181-191 (Box 12)
    - Special Acts, 1-9 (Box 12)
    - Special Session, June - Resolutions (Box 13)
    - Special Session, June - Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 13)
    - Special Session, July - Resolutions (Box 13)
    - Special Session, Public Act, 1 (Box 13)
    - Unfinished Business - No Committee Name, Aging, Appropriations (Box 13)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Children; Commerce (Box 14)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Energy and Technology; Environment; Executive and Legislative Nominations; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 15)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 16)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections; Higher Education and Employment Advancement; Housing; Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 17)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 18)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 19)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Planning and Development; Program Review and Investigations; Public Health; Public Safety (Box 20)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; Veterans' Affairs; Senate Calendar, Resolutions to SB-61 (Box 21)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-63 to SB-277 (Box 22)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-284 to SB-327 (Box 23)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-329 to SB-374 (Box 24)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-389 to SB-434 (Box 25)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-435 to SB-467 (Box 26)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, SB-468 to HB-5143 (Box 27)
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, HB-5147 to HB-5421 (Box 28)